<form>
  <field>
    <id>general.enabled</id>
    <label>Enabled</label>
    <type>checkbox</type>
    <help>Enable the AdGuard Home service.</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.setupuser</id>
    <label>Admin User</label>
    <type>text</type>
    <help>Admin username for the AdGuard Home web interface. Managed by the plugin (AdGuard Home has no UI to change it).</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.setuppassword</id>
    <label>Admin Password</label>
    <type>password</type>
    <help>Admin password for the AdGuard Home web interface. Enter a value to set or change it; leave blank to keep the current password. Stored in config.xml and applied (bcrypt-hashed) to AdGuardHome.yaml on Save. If left blank on first setup, the web UI has no login until you set one.</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.webport</id>
    <label>Web Interface Port</label>
    <type>text</type>
    <help>TCP port for the AdGuard Home admin web interface. Set here (AdGuard Home has no UI to change its own admin port); also used for the "Open AdGuard Home" link below.</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.dnsport</id>
    <label>DNS Port</label>
    <type>text</type>
    <help>UDP/TCP port AdGuard Home listens on for DNS. Keep this a high port (e.g. 5353) so AdGuard Home runs unprivileged and does not clash with Unbound on 53 — point clients or Unbound at this port. (You can also change it in AdGuard Home's own UI, but the plugin re-asserts this value on Save.)</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.runas</id>
    <label>Run As User</label>
    <type>text</type>
    <help>System user used to run AdGuard Home. Defaults to the dedicated, unprivileged "adguardhome" account (least privilege). Because the plugin seeds a config before first start, AdGuard Home never needs root — leave this as "adguardhome" unless you have a specific reason to change it.</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.configpath</id>
    <label>Configuration File</label>
    <type>text</type>
    <help>Path to AdGuardHome.yaml. AdGuard Home owns and rewrites this file; the plugin seeds it and rewrites only the managed keys (admin user/password, web port, DNS port). Change only if you know what you are doing.</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.workdir</id>
    <label>Working Directory</label>
    <type>text</type>
    <help>Directory for AdGuard Home runtime data (filters, query log, statistics, sessions database).</help>
  </field>
  <field>
    <id>general.extraopts</id>
    <label>Extra Options</label>
    <type>text</type>
    <help>Additional command-line arguments passed to the AdGuard Home binary.</help>
  </field>
</form>
